truckaddons.com 2016-03-14

# Ordering Information at TruckAddons.com

Ordering From TruckAddons.com

Online Orders:  
TruckAddons.com provides a simple online ordering process to serve our customers. We offer hundreds of thousands of parts for online purchase and over 1 million parts orderable over the telephone. To place your order online, navigate TruckAddons.com and find the products you'd like to purchase. Press the "Add to Cart" button for the product. The product will be added to your shopping cart. You may continue to shop or check out by pressing the "Go to Secure Checkout" button. Choose your payment method and then enter your billing, shipping and contact information. Once you complete the checkout process you will be sent an order confirmation to the email address you provided during the checkout process.  
  
Phone Orders:  
If you would like to place your order by phone, use our toll free number  1-859-231-8120. Our automotive accessory specialists are available Monday - Saturday 9am to 6pm EST. Feel free to find the item your interested in online and call in to place the order, or we can help you get the right part for your vehicle.

TruckAddons.com proudly accepts the following payment methods.

|   
  
---  
Credit Card Charges:  
Credit card charges will be from _**Truck and Auto Extras**_ , the parent company of TruckAddons.com.  

In most cases we will provide you with a tracking number within 3-5 business days of placing your order without having to request it. Most orders are processed and shipped within this time frame.

TruckAddons.com ships from our main warehouse in Lexington Kentucky, but we also ship from multiple warehouses across the country as well as shipping directly from 500+ manufacturers straight to you when needed. This can cause delays in providing the customer a tracking number. Often, customers will receive their order before we are able to supply them their tracking number on drop ship or factory direct orders. If you would like to request a tracking number, please use the tracking request form. 

In most cases, products ordered from TruckAddons.com will ship within 24-48 hours of placement (EXCLUDING weekends and holidays). On occasion, parts will need to be custom made/factory special ordered. When a product must be special ordered from the manufacturer or when a product is backordered the delivery time will in most cases increase. 

In order to ensure the protection and security of your personal information, Trailblazers/TruckAddons.com utilizes secure line technology at TruckAddons.com. Our cart has built-in security measures to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your information. Your credit card information is protected using 128-bit (SSL) encryption technology, and is SET compliant. To insure that no one other than our company receives your information, all you private information is encrypted.

While we continually make every effort to reflect current price and inventory status, occasionally prices will differ from those listed on our web site. TruckAddons.com reserves the right to change prices at any time, and to infor the customer of the price change before charging your credit card or proceeding with the order. If the price of a part on your order has changed, we will inform you via phone or email and request authorization for the new price to be charged. At this time, you will also have the option of canceling the part from your order or switching to a different part.

TruckAddons.com is not responsible for part numbers/descriptions that are changed or superceded by the manufacturer. We strive to keep the information listed on our web site up to date, but occasionally a part will be changed/superceded/discontinued without our knowledge. Our product descriptions are taken directly from the manufacturer's catalogs and web sites. We are only able to provide the description that the manufacturer has supplied us with, and we cannot be held responsible for discrepancies in these descriptions. In some occurrences the images displayed on a product page may not reflect the exact part ordered.

If you wish to cancel an order placed during business hours, we must receive an order cancellation request [****](mailto:customer_service@truckaddons.com)within THIRTY MINUTES of your order being placed. Any cancellation requests received after this time will be examined on a case-by-case basis. We offer no guarantee that your order will be able to be cancelled after this time period. If your order is placed outside business hours, your email MUST be received by 9AM EST. on the following business day. Again, cancellation requests submitted outside this time period are NOT guaranteed, and are examined case-by-case.

  * All shipping, processes and freight charges are non refundable.
  * Must receive a confirmation email from TruckAddons to ensure your cancellation is complete 

Orders placed online cannot be cancelled by a phone call alone. You must complete the cancellation request form. If we do not receive a cancellation form request for your online order Truckaddons.com will not be responsible for lack of cancellation.

TruckAddons.com is not able to accept credit cards drawn on international banks at this time. We are able to accept international PayPal payments, as long as the merchandise is being shipped to the verified shipping address on your PayPal account. TruckAddons.com's preferred method of payment for international orders is via bank wire transfer. If you wish to obtain the account information to wire a payment, please email: [**orders@truckaddons.com.**](mailto:orders@truckaddons.com)

Personal Information Privacy Policy:   
In order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customer, we offer the following guarantee regarding information gathering and dissemination practices for our web site. By shopping at TruckAddons.com, you are guaranteed that.

TruckAddons.com will not under any circumstances sell or release your personal information to a non involved third party. This includes Credit Card Numbers, Email Addresses, Name, Phone Numbers and any other personal information that we may posses. 

Email Privacy Policy 

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

Why did you receive an email from us?

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.  
  
**How we protect your privacy** **** We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system. 

Sharing and Usage

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. 

How can you stop receiving email from us?

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.

**Remarketing:**  
Remarketing allows TruckAddons.com to reach out to our visitors in banner advertisements outside of our site with targeted advertisements based upon the products that you viewed during your time on our site using Google, and other third party vendors. These vendors, including Google, utilize a cookie to identify you on their display networks and serve you banner advertisements based on your previous visit(s) to our site. If you choose, you can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads).

| 

| 

Call Toll Free   
1-859-231-8120  
  
---|---  

| 

Our Email Support Page Email Support   
  
---|---  

| 

View shipping information   
Shipping Policy   
  
---|---  

| 

Submit a Tracking Request   
Tracking Request   
  
---|---  

| 

Secure Online Ordering   
Secure Server   
  
---|---  

| 

Return an item   
Returns Request   
  
---|---  

| 

File a Damage Claim   
Damage Claims   
  
---|---  

| 

Request an exchange   
Exchange Item   
  
---|---  

| 

Cancel an Order  
Cancellation Form  
  
---|---
